OUR STICKY LOVE
This is it.
What?
Goodbye, Go Eun-sae.
What do you mean?
Where are you telling me to go, alone?
Jang Tae-ha!
Jang Tae-ha.
What's with the strange dream?
Actually, no.
What about our marriage?
Is that not happening?
I guess it isn't that strange,
since he doesn't even like me.
Now that her memory has returned,
this whole act is over.
Pretending to be her boyfriend,
being all close…
Starting tomorrow, you can't do that.
Are you okay?
Don't act as if you care.
I know now that you don't.
So you remember all of it?
What kind of person Jang Tae-ha really is.
I know everything now.
Yes.
So what will you do now?
Now that everything's out in the open,
are you going to be honest?
I know you must be confused.
I'm sorry if our time together
was unpleasant.
It was the best I could do.
Pretending we dated to bring you here.
I couldn't leave you alone.
Why not?
Because you pitied me?
I may have lost my memory,
but I never asked for sympathy.
Why didn't you just abandon me?
As you now know,
you have to leave.
I found a place for you to go.
You can leave next week. Until then,
stay here even if it's uncomfortable.
Sorry for everything.
So people really do change overnight.
I've just gone back to my old self.
I really can't believe any of this,
so I'll ask you one last time.
So you're saying
that everything you said and did for me
was all fake?
Yes.
That it was all an act?
Go Eun-sae.
Why did you have to…
Get a grip, Go Eun-sae!
This isn't the time to get angry.
It's time for you to leave.
Stay here. I'll go buy some ointment.
JUNGANG PHARMACY
Go Eun-sae.
Go Eun-sae!
If she remembered it all,
she should've been terrified.
Where on earth did she go?
You don't think she went
to the Seoul Prosecutor's Office, do you?
Seoul is Baek Sang-gil's turf,
so she could be in real danger.
And she left her phone.
The fastest way to find her would be
to check the cameras from here to town.
We'd need to report her missing,
but her identity is…
Hey, don't worry about that.
I've been drinking buddies with
the local police chief for a decade.
Is there a party going on?
Why are you all swarming out?
Where's our girl, Eun-sae?
Did you happen to see her?
What are you talking about?
- We made it over here to comfort her.
- Comfort her?
There's no such thing as secrets
in a teeny village like this.
I heard she drank heaps
at the pub yesterday
because someone left her
completely torn up inside.
Sorry?
Fine! I'll say a few words as your elder.
You, Tae-ha!
You shouldn't do that.
A woman's heart is fragile, easily broken
with a spoonful of cheap sympathy.
You'd lost feelings a long while ago,
but you still held her hand everywhere.
Treated her like a princess!
That's deceit! Deceit is what that is!
That's right.
What are you going to say next?
That Muhammed Ali got beaten up?
What did he do to hear all this
cheap sympathy and deceit nonsense?
- What?
- Hold up.
What are you all talking about?
What are you talking about?
Wait, so it's not like that?
I guess not.
- Well…
- Well, you see…
We thought it was like that,
so that's what we told her.
We didn't want Eun-sae to end up
being the fool.
And what exactly did you tell her?
- Well…
- We just…
Tae-ha, you said
you weren't going to marry her.
Yeah, that she had no memory
and no place to go,
so you let her stay out of pity.
That you don't see her that way.
Sorry?
Isn't that why you two fought yesterday?
Yeong-sil from the pub said so.
That Eun-sae kept saying,
"Why did you do all that
when you had no intention of marrying me?"
What the…
Poor Eun-sae.
So she wasn't drinking yesterday
because her memory returned?
GUJIN-GUN OFFICE
Hello. How can I help you?
I'm an unidentified person with no family.
I have amnesia, so I don't know who I am.
As for my identity…
Goodness.
I couldn't find it because of this.
I want to go to a government facility
that protects people like me.
Darn it.
So this was because you misunderstood,
as did all of you?
All of this happened
because of a misunderstanding?
- A misunderstanding?
- A mis…
- Misunderstanding?
- How…
Hey, where are you going all of a sudden?
- We need to check the CCTV footage now.
- Right.
- There's Eun-sae, getting in a taxi.
- Yeah.
Wait.
- Isn't that Dal-su's taxi?
- Yeah!
Go on, then. Hurry and call Dal-su.
Yeah.
Good heavens.
Oh boy.
Tae-ha, I know it's important
to go and find your wife,
but we still have
a lot of life left to live too!
I still need to see Pil-seung get married!
- Oh, Tae-ha!
- Goodness.
- Sir!
- Goodness, Tae-ha!
It's locked. Tae-ha, they're closed.
- What's wrong?
- What is it? What?
Tae-ha!
How'd he do that?
If you know Ji-won,
you must know where she is.
Where is she?
I'll ask you first.
What's your relationship with Ms. Ji-won?
You didn't come here knowing everything?
Please answer me first.
Ji-won is my girlfriend.
She's been missing for over a month.
Do you have proof?
Have a scroll through.
If the photos aren't proof enough,
you can go to the Prosecutors' Office.
- Prosecutors' Office?
- Yes.
Prosecutor Go and I…
Most of the guards, investigators,
and her fellow prosecutors knew about us.
Prosecutor?
Where is Ji-won?
Gujin doesn't have any facilities.
They say you have to go
all the way to Dangjin.
You'll stay at a temporary
homeless shelter for a few days
before moving to a self-support center.
My goodness, to lose your entire memory…
Usually, people have at least someone
by their side in situations like these.
Do you really not have anyone?
Good grief!
Damn it.
What the heck was that for?
You can't just do that.
You're asking for an accident, you know!
I'm her husband.
She's not alone.
She has me by her side.
What?
And she has sisters.
And a super obedient little brother.
And a slightly older brother-in-law.
And a friend who transcends age.
What's going on here?
What is all this?
That guy risked all our lives
to come here.
He drove like it was a roller coaster.
He even jumped over
the totem-pole-high county office gates.
I thought he was going to take flight.
Why go to such lengths…
Why do you think?
He was worried
that he might lose his wife.
That makes no sense.
You told me to go.
To leave.
That was all our fault.
We shouldn't have gotten involved.
Turns out, we made you
misunderstand each other.
Sorry.
You weren't keeping me around
because you pitied me?
That dog of yours.
The dog.
He was talking about the dog.
You actually believed that?
You said you didn't even see me that way.
That was about Su-ji.
I'm so nervous I can barely breathe,
even now.
But you said you wouldn't marry me!
Because everything you know about us
is based on what I told you.
When your memory comes back…
If, when your memory returns…
If you still
feel that way about me…
then…
give me permission
to marry you.
Are you serious?
You don't hate me?
I can really stay?
Go Eun-sae.
Let's go
home.
It really felt like my world was ending.
I was fearful of living without you.
It felt so much like hell.
Silly me. I'm tearing up.
Right?
Goodness me.
Why are you crying, young man?
I cry whenever I see someone else cry.
I bet their hands are all sweaty.
What…
What is all this?
There's a reason we call him
Taffy Village's Choi Soo-jong.
- Looks like her.
- Go on, then. Hurry and call Dal-su.
- Yeah, okay.
- Goodness.
It's a good thing
she got in Dal-su's taxi.
- What is this?
- What's this?
What is all this?
Did you order these
right after she said she liked
light pink roses yesterday morning?
Deceit, my foot.
Darn it.
Let me call Dal-su…
Is this because
I said light pink roses are pretty?
You like them.
Honestly.
You're impossible.
I was just talking about a bouquet.
There's no middle ground with this guy.
As a boxer, he only won gold medals.
No silvers.
Then, at school,
he was always last in his class.
Come on, Coach.
It's just so pretty.
Why don't you take a picture?
Yes! It's so pretty.
It's so pretty. You two should dress up
like a bride and groom.
And take a picture here.
Sounds good.
Can we do that?
I'd like to take a picture.
Okay.
Okay, we'll take the picture now.
The bride and groom.
Please hold hands.
- What are you waiting for?
- How sweet!
Okay, here goes. Three, two, one.
- That's it.
- Perfect!
How pretty.
Okay, now face each other.
- That's it!
- Look at each other.
More. Face each other.
Now, groom, hold out your hands.
Bride, place your hands on his.
That's nice.
Now look at the camera.
Three, two, one!
- You look lovely.
- Take care.
- You look good.
- Take care, sir.
Do well.
Good night.
- You too.
- Bye, So-wol.
- See you.
- Good night.
Congratulations? What is this, a wedding?
Honestly.
- Good night.
- One second.
Now the misunderstanding
has all been cleared up,
and this young man won't be around,
which means tonight
is your first night alone.
Goodness gracious!
I hope you don't wake up the whole village
in the middle of the night.
You're absolutely crazy.
Tae-ha, what makes a man?
Confidence, okay?
On a night like tonight,
a bed isn't a piece of furniture.
It's a stage.
In bed, a man must be confident!
Please stop.
We'll take care of it ourselves.
- Yourselves?
- They'll take care of it?
Themselves?
Please hurry home.
- Get home safe.
- Goodbye.
I don't know why they're like that.
Well…
Yeah, well…
Shall we…
Shall we have a drink?
Wow, you had something like this?
You must be a total drinker,
carrying something like this around
and drinking by yourself.
You drank with me.
I did? When?
In Japan. Under the cherry blossoms.
Cherry blossoms?
This place is so beautiful.
It must have been so romantic.
I want my memory to return soon.
It's so unfair that you're the only one
who remembers all of that good stuff.
Perfect.
By the way,
what was it about what I said
that you misunderstood?
What?
The harsh things you said to me earlier
sounded so real.
It scared me a little.
The time we spent together
in Taffy Village…
I thought
you hated it all.
There's no way.
Someday, when time passes
and your memory returns,
and even if the day comes
when you don't like me anymore,
I hope our time together
won't be a painful memory for you.
You really like me, don't you?
Worrying about things you don't need to.
There's no way I'd ever not like you.
But why do you like me so much?
- You're p--
- Don't say it's because I'm pretty.
That's so cliché.
I was going to say
it's because you're polite.
What?
Say that again.
You're actually quite polite,
subtly taking care of Grandma.
And up until a moment ago,
you spoke formally to me.
Seriously, stop joking around.
Tell me why you really like me. Now.
I don't know.
Come on, you really have nothing to say?
I really don't know. I just
don't like other women.
When I'm with you, I get…
a little weird.
You know what?
I'm like that too.
I get nervous, too,
when I'm with you.
I can barely breathe.
Now I like you more than Cha Eun-woo.
And the password to my new email
is "Jang Tae-ha."
The first face that comes to mind
when I wake up,
and the last face that comes to mind
before I go to sleep, is Jang Tae-ha's.
I like you.
A lot.
Gi-jun, what brings you here--
What the hell are you up to?
- What?
- I know everything.
Who she really is, who you've been hiding.
Anti-corruption Prosecutor Go Ji-won
from the Seoul Prosecutors' Office.
Tell me.
How did you know?
I just met with Gwak Chi-hyeon.
Go Eun-sae… I mean, Prosecutor Go Ji-won.
He's looking for her.
How do you know about him?
How much did you tell him?
- Did you tell him that she's here?
- Answer me first.
What happened?
Do you know that this is a crime?
Gi-jun, let's talk for a second.
I need to meet Chairman Baek.
So, you saved Go Eun-sae
when you were supposed to kill her,
and you pretended to be her boyfriend
to keep her safe.
And because she would only agree to flee
if she regained her memory,
you were sincere about her treatment.
Is that right?
So they really, you know,
make you… kill people and stuff?
The man you met, Gwak Chi-hyeon,
is one of Baek Sang-gil's men.
If he knows that she's alive,
he'll probably tell Baek Sang-gil.
Now tell me.
How much did you tell Gwak Chi-hyeon?
Everything?
Well…
I don't even know why I did that.
Where is Ji-won?
I think I'm in the wrong place.
Sorry?
The Go Ji-won I know is not this person.
What is this all of a sudden?
This Go Ji-won… I mean, another Go Ji-won
has caused a lot of harm
to a lot of people.
So I was looking for her,
but it seems they just share
the same name.
Then how did you get my number?
Well,
I had someone look into
Go Ji-won's acquaintances,
but I think the private investigator
made a mistake.
Anyway, I don't know this person.
I apologize for the inconvenience.
Wait. Excuse me?
You and I were never that close,
and we were polar opposites,
the top student and the bottom student.
But I know you're not a bad guy.
I wanted to hear you out first
before deciding whether to hand her over
to Gwak Chi-hyeon or call the cops.
Right, thanks.
I really mean it. Thanks, Gi-jun.
No problem.
But
if Go Eun-sae never gets her memory back,
what are you going to do?
I'll have to force her to leave.
But if I do that,
Go Eun-sae will be devastated.
I actually meant to ask.
Is there really no way
to get her memory back faster?
The treatment's already brought back
some of her memory.
Like her remembering Gwak Chi-hyeon.
From now on,
you need to help her see, feel,
and experience things from her past
to trigger any memories related to them.
I've been dying to ask you.
What's with all these flowers?
What?
Oh, these?
Go Eun-sae said roses are pretty.
And women,
they like this sort of thing?
What?
Never mind.
I'm going.
Okay.
Can I take one of these?
Yeah, sure. You can take a lot.
These roses are unique.
That bastard.
He's so damn cool.
- Trouble?
- Yes.
I keep thinking that Prosecutor Go
might have gotten into some trouble.
If today was about sending someone
to test the waters,
he should have asked me something.
But he didn't ask me anything significant.
What are the chances
of a true coincidence?
No, he definitely reacted
to the photos of Prosecutor Go.
She got into some trouble…
Maybe she got seriously injured
or was kidnapped by someone.
That's why I came to see you, sir.
Please trace the phone number
of the man I met today.
I'm sure he is somehow connected
to Prosecutor Go.
Come on.
On such an important night,
why did I have to go and get wasted
and fall asleep?
Stupid.
That's right.
Last night.
I remember
the atmosphere was really tense.
Why would the two of them be like that?
Did they fight over me?
What am I going to do?
You're up?
Jang Tae-ha.
Doctor An came by last night, didn't he?
Yes.
How did you know?
I thought I saw him
when I briefly woke up.
Don't worry too much.
I'll give him a serious talking-to.
WE UNDERSTAND YOUR FEELINGS
Lean back comfortably for a bit.
I'm not comfortable
because of you, Doctor.
Sorry?
I think I should say this
before we start the treatment.
Since you came all the way
to our home last night.
I know we've gotten a lot closer recently.
I got drunk, and you carried me home.
I must have made a scene.
But that wasn't a sign
that you could cross the line.
I'm in a common-law marriage.
We haven't had a wedding yet,
but we're practically married.
And I really,
really like Jang Tae-ha.
So I'm sorry,
but I hope we can remain
as a doctor and a patient.
What is this nonsense?
Did you drink again?
What?
Wow, this is…
This is bad. My goodness.
Where do I even start? Okay.
I'm sorry, but Ms. Go Eun-sae,
you're not my type.
I like women who look pure and innocent
and have eyes
that point to twenty past eight.
But looking at you now,
your eyes are more… thirteen past nine.
And what's more,
I don't like women who are too tall.
I have a bad neck, so…
Then why did you suddenly come to see
Jang Tae-ha last night
and look up at him
like you were picking a fight?
Hey, I did not look up at him!
We were totally eye to eye!
You were looking up at him like this!
Ms. Eun-sae, sit down, okay?
- Wait a second.
- You're here for treatment.
I'm done. Let's go.
Have a safe trip home.
I like women who look pure and innocent
and have eyes
that point to twenty past eight.
Just put something down.
- Just wait.
- Oh, come on!
- Seriously?
- Did you see that?
- How the heck?
- Here goes!
What even is this?
A double sweep. Cough up two cards each.
Come on!
All the top cards are going to you today.
And you got all the double junk cards.
It's your lucky day.
Tell me about it.
I wonder what good thing
is going to happen to me…
Should I buy a lottery ticket?
I avoided the penalty.
Isn't that Pil-seung?
Oh my.
He's marching over here like Lee Jung-jae
in The Face Reader.
Let's go. Come on.
Wait, Mom.
Oh, shut it.
Mom, please.
Why does it have to be fist fights?
I raised you for 17 years, making sure
you never got a single scratch.
And now you want me
to watch some scary punks
whack you on the head?
I won't get whacked. I'll hit them harder.
All right. Let's say you do well
and even win a medal.
What will you do after you retire?
Who'd hire a guy who fought for a living?
People will just call you empty-headed
wherever you go.
- What if I fill my head?
- What's this now?
If I'm good at boxing and get smart,
no one will be able to say that.
You're going to study?
You're the last in your whole school.
If I do well on the next mock exam,
let me box.
Is that a deal or not?
What's wrong?
Why are you… A report card?
- A report card?
- It's Pil-seung's.
What place…
Fifth… in the whole school.
Fifth in your school?
Pil-seung! Goodness, Hui-ja!
There's no doubt about it.
It's five, just like five top cards!
Five!
Fine, you can box.
You must have really wanted this
if you went from last to fifth place.
I'm going to the nationals
in two days' time.
But
can you go there just like that?
I applied three months ago.
I planned on competing anyway.
But you haven't been able to train
because you've been studying.
No. I haven't taken
a single day off from training.
Other than eating and pooping,
I studied and trained
as if my life depended on it.
Now that you know,
I thought I'd be up front
and ask permission.
Okay.
A promise is a promise.
You can compete in that thingy.
You mean that?
But
I'm not going.
I can't bear to see someone
whacking you in the head.
Don't make me sit through that too.
Please look after him.
Mrs. Pang…
I heard that Prosecutor Go Ji-won is alive
and that she's holding a knife
to our throats.
How did you find out about that?
Did you really think
that when my previous aide
made a mess and still survived you,
I wouldn't have him tailed?
Well, well.
I didn't know
our mayor was capable of that.
I wonder why someone in silk robes
would dirty themselves with mud.
Then you should have cleaned up properly!
You couldn't even handle
a rookie nobody prosecutor
and left crumbs behind?
Makes me uneasy.
The party is all in, building me up
as a presidential candidate.
Momentum's good.
I'm close to moving into the house
adorned with the rose of Sharon.
Don't sully it.
I buried 11 corpses
under the roots of that rose of Sharon.
If I, Baek Sang-gil, were to become
a mad dog and dig up that land…
they'd all come out into the open.
Could you handle that?
So,
let's not waste time
barking at each other.
I'm looking for her,
and I won't let anything go wrong.
- I'll be going now, Coach.
- Yeah, good work.
- Goodbye.
- Bye.
- Get home safe.
- You got it!
Pil-seung is awesome.
So youthful spirit wins everything.
Oh, right!
I want to go cheer for Pil-seung
at his match.
It's too dangerous to leave…
You need to help her see, feel,
and experience things from her past.
Okay, let's go together.
Really? Yay!
That one. Is that yours?
Yeah, it's a medal I got back
thanks to my first love.
Why are you bringing up
your first love right now?
Do you want to hit this if you're angry?
Mention your first love again and see
what happens. I'm the jealous type.
By the way, I was in your room yesterday.
It's so drafty in there.
No, it's not.
Yes, it is.
Why don't you sleep in my room from now on
so you don't catch a cold?
Is that all you think about?
Yes, of course.
I only think about you all day long.
We're not sharing a bed.
And why not?
I told you. You make me nervous.
I need to prepare myself.
Fine.
Then I'll give you a few days
to prepare yourself.
I think I've gained some weight recently,
so I should get back in shape.
You haven't.
You're pretty.
So you know the right answer.
Quite a master at flirting, aren't you?
Be honest.
You've dated a lot, haven't you?
- I haven't.
- As if.
I'll forgive you if you tell me now.
But you have to tell me now.
Be honest.
THE 107TH NATIONAL SPORTS FESTIVAL
HIGH SCHOOL BOXING MATCH
We need to get the confetti ready.
BOXING ARENA
Ladies!
- There you are.
- Over here.
- We're coming.
- What is all this?
This is amazing!
We're Pil-seung's aunties
who even changed his diapers.
- This is the least we can do.
- Yeah.
In case folks look down on him
for being from the country.
Who would look down on him
after seeing this?
We're like some kind of gang right now.
Oh, come on.
Pil-seung is coming out.
I think it's starting.
There! Pil-seung!
The pride of Gujin!
- Kim Pil-seung, go get them!
- You've got this!
Go, Pil-seung!
- It's starting.
- Tae-ha.
Look at me. Are you nervous?
Do your best.
- Pil-seung has…
- Taffy fists!
KO! Red corner wins by KO!
ROUND OF 16
OH SEUNG-HYEON VS KIM PIL-SEUNG
QUARTERFINALS
JUNG GANG-SAN VS KIM PIL-SEUNG
SEMIFINALS
JOO YEONG-MIN VS KIM PIL-SEUNG
That's it! Back away now.
FINAL
GUJIN HIGH, KIM PIL-SEUNG
VS YONGDEOK HIGH, CHOI WON-UK
The high school boxing final
will begin shortly.
Pil-seung, this is the last match.
You've done great.
Don't get nervous
and stay focused until the end, okay?
Let's go!
Swing your arms!
More!
That's it! Again!
Get off him.
Damn it!
Excuse me. Please move aside!
Hold on.
Pil-seung, are you okay?
Oh no, what do we do?
Don't you even maintain
the facilities here?
Oh dear. This isn't the kind of bleeding
that will stop anytime soon.
It looks pretty serious,
so we should end the match now.
Let's rule it a loss by decision
for Kim Pil-seung.
No, you can't!
You can't do that.
You should reschedule the match!
According to the rules,
it's up to me, the TD, to decide
whether to reschedule or rule it a loss.
So reschedule the match.
We can do it some other day!
Come on, you know how it is.
Don't you know how complicated it is
to reschedule a match?
Then you'd be happy for us
to take legal action?
- Sorry?
- It's in Article 2 of the Civil Act.
The organizers of a sports event
have a duty, in good faith,
to protect athletes during a competition.
In this case, not only was the athlete
injured due to the organizers' negligence,
he now risks losing his chance at gold.
You tell them!
If this isn't resolved properly,
we will file a lawsuit for breach of duty
regarding injury and medical treatment.
- That's right!
- Yes, a lawsuit!
Then please wait
in the waiting room for now.
- What the heck?
- What are you playing at?
How long do you expect us to wait?
Is he okay?
Pil-seung, are you okay?
- How is it?
- Can I take a look?
He's bleeding too much.
- Oh dear. What if it scars?
- This is so upsetting.
By the way,
how did you know so much
about the law earlier?
Yeah, exactly.
- You sounded like a judge or a prosecutor.
- Yeah.
That's what I'm saying.
I don't know how,
but the words just flew out of my mouth.
Before I lost my memory,
maybe I was a pro…
- A pro…
- A pro what?
A pro…
A prodigy!
- You were amazing.
- You're smart.
You're amazing.
Or properly scary.
- Surprising, yeah?
- She's smart.
I want the rematch today.
You…
- You're in no state to--
- I can do it.
I don't want a silver medal.
I'll do the rematch today.
Please let him do that.
The bleeding has almost stopped,
and an athlete knows his body best.
The flow of the match was good today,
so Pil-seung must have a good feeling.
BOXING ASSOCIATION OF KOREA
NO ENTRY
Hey!
We told you to go back for now.
The referees and officials
are discussing it,
so if you wait in the waiting room,
we'll let you know.
Hey!
I won't put a silver medal
around my boy's neck like this!
Even if he gets a silver medal,
it happens today, you hear?
Please!
Let him fight today in his gloves
for whatever medal!
Okay?
Are you listening?
You hear?
How did it go?
Have a seat.
Are you sure
you're up for it?
Okay.
Pil-seung.
It's okay to lose.
For not giving up
and keeping your gloves on until the end,
you've already won gold in my eyes.
I have a favor to ask.
Just don't get hurt.
FINAL
KIM PIL-SEUNG VS CHOI WON-UK
Please.
- Pil-seung.
- Pil-seung, you've got this!
Come on, Pil-seung!
Go, taffy fists!
That's it.
Yeah, that's it.
- Circle more.
- Keep moving!
Get closer!
- Oh my!
- Do it!
- Stay on him! Corner him!
- Lead hand.
- Oh no!
- Guard up.
Red, back to your corner.
Red corner wins by KO!
Pil-seung, good job!
Great job, Pil-seung!
Come here.
Good job!
Pil-seung, you did great!
You did well. You were great.
You did great.
Great work. Congratulations on gold.
Coach!
Wait one second.
Why are you crying? I won.
This is why!
This is why I didn't want you to fight.
Goodness, just look at your face.
Did you really have to go
all the way to the end?
You could have waited
until you were better.
Did you really
have to go as far as to draw blood?
Because of you, Mom.
If I had a rematch on another day,
you'd have to cry again.
Red corner wins by KO!
Advancing to the final, red corner.
Seeing you there gave me strength.
That's why I won.
Thanks for coming, Mom.
You rascal.
You rascal!
You damn rascal!
Why did I even give birth to you?
Okay.
It's okay, Mom.
Why did you give birth to me?
So you could see me
win a gold medal, of course.
Good job, my baby.
I'm so proud of you, my son.
I didn't even know
my Pil-seung was this amazing.
I'm sorry I didn't know.
It's okay.
You're crying again?
Young man, maybe you should get checked
for menopause?
I'm in my twenties.
What?
- He said he's in his twenties.
- Tae-ha.
- This is perfectly fine.
- Still, stop it.
It'll hurt.
It doesn't hurt. I'm a gold medalist.
- Are we having a feast at Pil-seung's?
- Barbecue?
- Damn right.
- Yeah, let's.
- Hui-ja's treat.
- What are we eating?
Let's just eat at home.
Let's have some barbecue…
They look great.
It feels like I'm watching
a TV show's happy ending.
Wasn't I also like a character
in a TV show today?
Wasn't I sort of awesome earlier?
Where did that come from earlier?
Did you remember something?
I don't really know
where it came from either.
It does sort of feel like
I've done that before.
If I'm honest, I've felt kind of weird
since I got here today.
I feel like I've been here before.
Is this the only boxing arena?
No.
But I like this one the most.
Why?
I met my first love here.
That darn first love of yours
is really getting on my nerves.
It was nice meeting you,
Mr. Future Gold Medalist.
What was his name again?
I want to remember it.
What? Did you remember something else?
Yes.
I think I met some guy here
a long time ago.
Do you remember anything else?
No.
I don't remember any details,
but I think that guy was really
handsome.
- What?
- He had a really good vibe, and…
Right!
He said he was a future gold medalist.
Yeah.
And judging by
how I kept glancing back wistfully,
I think I must have liked that guy a lot.
He was handsome.
That's why you should stop
talking about your first love.
I just don't remember him now,
but I had a guy like that too.
Wait for me.
Jang Tae-ha,
I'm off to work at the taffy workshop.
Is this yours, sir?
OUR STICKY LOVE
Subtitle translation by: Jimin Choi